[Music]
welcome back you're still watching
business lunch and an important story we
understand from sources that a whole
host of suitors have submitted
expressions of interest for reliance
capital ritu singh my colleague joins us
with all of the details srithu what are
you picking up
thanks for that well a record number of
suitors have actually come forward to
submit an expression of interest to
acquire reliance capital which is a core
investment company and its various group
businesses under the insolvency and
bankruptcy law as the deadline ended
over the weekend we've been given to
understand that from banks nbfcs private
equity players lots of insurance
companies arcs and other financial
institutions have shown interest these
include the likes of pyramid finance
bandhan financial holdings indecent
international yes bank motilal oswal
financial services punawala finance
adani finsev among insurance companies
you have icici lombard tata aig htfc
ergo nippon life insurance zurich
international from private equity
players there's the likes of oak creek
brookfield blackstone tpg kkr
you know asset reconstruction companies
like iarc so all of these players have
come forward we'll have to see how many
of these actually get converted into
binding bids remember eois had been
invited both for reliance capital as an
entity and also for eight clusters of
businesses uh businesses which are
divided into insurance wealth finance
real estate arc business and so on uh
lenders of course we've been given to
understand will give a preference to
those that have bid for the cic as a
whole so we'll have to see how this
proceeds over 30 000 crores of claims
have been made by financial creditors
but the bulk of the debt is actually
held by bondholders all right thanks
ritu for all those exclusive details so
our